[{"answer": "Well, I think you just jinxed it, Piers, because unfortunately the weather is set to change and there are predictions we will have a few showers on Friday, but it's April and Britain is known for having April showers.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "What's happened?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "I mean it is tangible.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "How does it feeling to you?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "ICHOLL: Yes.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, it's true that not everyone wishes the happy couple, you know, a very peaceful day.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What have we heard about this?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Well, obviously there's been a massive security operation in London and good security is invisible security.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What kind of preparations has there been security wise for this event?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "I've played them.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, I think this is Britain at its greatest, at its best.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Why is this such a huge event do you think?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Did you ever meet Diana?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "She was really normal.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "And what was she like?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "And America in particular is going crazy.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "I mean they're kind of looking around saying, all this countries want to know about our -- you know, our royal wedding and think it's a huge thing?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I think Kate -- I've never met her, of course.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What do you think of Kate Middleton?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "I can't even imagine.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Can you even begin to imagine what it's like at the level that Kate Middleton is about to face?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, I think --", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "What advice would you give to the royal couple about marriage?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I have definitely cracked it.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "You've (INAUDIBLE) it out?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "I get so proud.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "When you come back to London, what do you feel when you come back and it's all exciting like this and there's this huge event?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Are you really?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think she's going to go for the huge big poofy thing that the Emanuels did for Diana.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "The dress?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I think she will wear some of the Queen's jewelry.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Jewelry?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Well, have the tiara and something floral in.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "And do what?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Just delicately.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "EYMOUR: Gosh.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What do you imagine he might want to say?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I was.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Were you?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I believe in the monarchy when it's done properly.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Do you believe in the monarchy?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I'll be right here, right next to you actually.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "And where will you be on big day?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "It's going to be so exciting.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "I mean it will be exciting, won't it?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "They are the royal --", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "How are you feeling about me being here with Anderson Cooper, Cat Deeley and Richard Quest, the royal wedding A-team?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "You panicking?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "And this is almost like our little club here, isn't it?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "It really does.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Elizabeth, this must bring back so many memories for you, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Absolutely no idea.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Have you any idea who has designed this dress?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Well, I'm sure it's not going to look anything like Diana's dress because that was really such an '80s kind of a look.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Is that the kind of feeling you're getting?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Jane was surmising it may be a combination of tiara and flowers.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "But I'm sure there'll be some fashion twists, something unexpected, you know?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, David and I at the time, we'd just left college, really, been out about a year.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "When you designed Diana's dress -- obviously, it was one of the world's most legendary dresses -- what kind of pressure did you feel as that designer?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I think she just liked us.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Why did Diana choose you, do you think?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "No, she never seemed to be under pressure.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Was Diana under -- I mean, obviously under huge pressure at the time, but did she show it to you when you were having all the fittings and stuff?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I think it's the whole build-up, actually.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Is that the most pressurized moment for you?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Oh, I think I would have loved to have done it.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Would you have liked to have made Kate's dress, or is once in a lifetime enough for this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you're going to see millions of copies of the dress everywhere.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "I mean, what will happen to the designer of Kate Middleton's dress, do you think?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Oh, there must be lots and lots.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Do you know how many brides got married in similar dresses to Diana's?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Are you excited about the wedding?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sure she would have really liked her.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What would she have made of Kate Middleton, do you think?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "MANUEL: Well, I don't know if that happened in the past, but Dave and I decided we would have a back-up and just in case anybody worked out what it was going to look like, we made another dress, different design, and it was hanging there all ready to go.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "If it gets snagged on the way out, do you have a spare dress?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "And yet nobody has a clue what it is.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, you know, after we got back to the studio and we were feeling a little bit deflated -- it had been such an amazing day, and it was all quiet.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "What did she say to you when she got a chance to talk to you again?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Well, we did, but then, you know, Dave and I split and we didn't have the business anymore.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Did you stay in touch with her over the years?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Could you sleep the night before?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Nothing went wrong.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Did anything go wrong on the day?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Oh, I would imagine, you know, if it's all handled properly, a lot of money.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "I mean, can you put a figure on what this might be worth to a designer in the modern day now?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "And if you were a betting woman -- are you a betting woman?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Well, everybody says it's Sarah Burton (ph).", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "If you were, given all the speculation about all the designers -- you know all these people -- who would you have your money on?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "It was absolutely fantastic.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "What was it like?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Absolutely normal.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "... were they resolutely normal?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Oh, traditional favorites, roast chicken, crispy roast potatoes, sausages and mash, and all the traditional English puddings.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Prince William -- what did he like and didn't like as a boy?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "I think probably the milk chocolate ones he enjoyed.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Milk chocolate?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Do you stay in touch with the royal family?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "I'm sure William follows in his footsteps, and I'm sure he's very keen on that.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "Do you think he'll be cracking the whip with his son, saying, Right, it's got to be healthy organic food?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "When he was younger, when he was a little boy, he enjoyed it.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "Is there any evidence he can cook?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "And did you?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "Oh, some chicken dishes and a couple of sweet things, as well, I think.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "What did you teach him?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "Possibly.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "Is he that kind of guy?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "That's one of the things he enjoys.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "It could be.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "Is that his, like, royal signature dish?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "OBB: I think it is.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "What was it -- when you were working for the royal family, is it a strange experience compared to a normal job, I mean, or would you get very quickly used to it?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "I think they were as normal as it was possible for them to be.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Can they be normal, the royals?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "Initially, I did.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Did you feel huge pressure when you prepared food?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "The details of it -- it was all such a terrifying experience, I can't remember the details.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "What was it?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "It had.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Had it all been eaten?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "She was absolutely incredible.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "What kind of lady was she?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "She was wonderful.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "What did you ask her?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "Yes, on a few occasions.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 800, "question": "Did you ever cook at the palace?", "qSentId": 799}, {"answer": "It was, yes, because our environment was very homely and quite intimate, the kitchens we had at Kensington Palace and Highgrove.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Is it intimidating to be in there and have to prepare meals?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "I'll be at home with my family.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 820, "question": "What are you doing on Friday?", "qSentId": 819}, {"answer": "Well, I'm working on a book at the moment, which is a food memoir, which is really my journey through the years and my food experiences growing up in South Africa.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 831, "question": "What is The Royal Touch?", "qSentId": 830}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "Like his lamb, William did?", "qSentId": 849}, {"answer": "No, exactly.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 865, "question": "And you can't really go wrong with that, can you?", "qSentId": 864}, {"answer": "Anytime.", "docId": "110425pmt", "aSentId": 867, "question": "And presumably, if she wants to, she can call you for some advice, can she, Kate?", "qSentId": 866}]